<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="https://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cutestrap</title>
    <description>A pure CSS framework with vertical rhythm, consistent form fields and a dead simple grid.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 23:44:08 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 23:44:08 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cutestrap Two Changelog</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;first-some-context&quot;&gt;First, some context.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since creating Cutestrap over 3 years ago now, I’ve used it as the foundation
for every side project I’ve worked on. After years of thoughts of what I would
want out of an upgrade, I’ve completely re-built it from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally, all of the vertical rhythm was hard coded, so all projects built
with Cutestrap looked somewhat the same. Version 1 was also written in Sass,
which restricted anyone not using it from unlocking all the customization
potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So! Cutestrap Two is written in 100% vanilla CSS and uses Custom Properties to
control the entire Baseline Grid and theme for way more customization options.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;whatever-whats-new-though&quot;&gt;Whatever, what’s new though?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Straight to the point, I dig it, dear reader.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Form fields can now be styled with consistent singular &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.field&lt;/code&gt; with children&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Custom Baseline Grid by changing a single Custom Property, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;--rhythm&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;More robust default color palette, using HSL&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Buttons are no longer styled implicitly and use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.button&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Way more button modifiers that can be composed together&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wrappers are now sized calculated based on rhythm&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Flexbox based grid system has removed in favor of a basic CSS Grid&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For a naming convention, BEM is out, Popsicle is in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To learn more, I highly recommend checking out the &lt;a href=&quot;/features&quot;&gt;Features&lt;/a&gt;
which documents all of the changes in more concrete detail.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/cutelog/cutestrap-two-changelog</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/cutelog/cutestrap-two-changelog</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
